&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：这一部分的大外卖。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Large takeaways
from this entire section.
所有这些都很酷，但是
All these are immediately cool, but
在这门课结束时，我会给你一个专业的建议。
I'm going to give you a pro
tip at the end of this course.
这些都不如将更少的JavaScript转移到浏览器中那么酷。
None of these are as cool as just
shifting less JavaScript to the browser.
对，因为你转换的JavaScript越少，这些东西就越不重要。
Right, because the less JavaScript you
shift, the less any of this stuff matters.
对，但是用户计时API，性能标记和
Right, but the user timing API,
the performance mark and
性能度量，这在您的实际应用程序中是非常有用的。
performance measure, that can be super
useful in your real world applications.
你可以继续，你现在就可以把它放进去，对吧，
You can go ahead, and
you can drop that in right now, right,
进入您的应用程序的某些部分，您怀疑它很慢，对吗？
into parts of your application that
you're suspicious of being slow, right?
你可以做录音，你可以看到我看到的那个更大的，而且
You can do the recording,
you can see that larger I saw, and
然后您可以实际操作，因为您比V8更了解您的代码。
then you can actual actions, cuz you know
your code better than v8 does right.
你可以继续
You can go ahead and
放下那一端，你实际上可以测量这个过程需要多长时间。
drop that end and you can actually
meter how long is this taking.
你可以做一件事，比如，一开始很酷，但是
You can do a thing, like,
that was cool for a start of time but
也许慢的东西拖着
maybe the slow thing is dragging and
在应用程序中删除某些内容，例如更新内容。
dropping something in your application,
like updating the thing.
如果你必须找出这个有多低，你实际上可以使用一个时间，
You can actually use a timing if you
have to find out how low is this,
这就是受伤的地方吗？
is this where the hurt is?
也许是，也许不是。
Maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
然后，最后我们看到可能使用类型系统
And then, finally we saw that
maybe using a type system
免费为您提供性能提升。
gives you performance gains for free.
我认为这也很有帮助。
I think that's really helpful as well.
很酷。
Very cool.
我们休息一下吃午饭吧。
Let's break for lunch.
然后我们会进入浏览器
And then we'll actually
get into the browser and
看看我们看到的JavaScript是怎样的。
see how everything we saw JavaScript.
这是如何与HTML和CSS以及dom和所有那些疯狂的东西交互的。
How does this interact with HTML and
CSS and the dom and all that crazy stuff.
我们将实际看到网页是如何诞生的。
We'll actually see how web pages are born.
一只鹳实际上把它们带到了浏览器，这很酷。
A stork actually brings them to
the browser, it's very cool.
从云中，它从云中下降，并带来它们，这是非常酷的。
From the cloud, it descends out of
the cloud and brings them, it's very cool.
好吧。
All right.